Finding Aid to the Nancy Stoller Papers, 1981-1995 MSS 2000-6
University of California, San Francisco Archives & Special Collections
Nancy Stoller papers
1981-1995
University of California, San Francisco Archives & Special Collections
Stoller, Nancy E.
MSS 2000-6
9 cartons, 1 oversize box, 1 oversize folder 14
Linear feet: 14
physdesc: Number of containers: 9 cartons, 1 oversize box, 1 oversize folder Linear feet: 14
This collection contains the research and writing files Nancy Stoller [who also worked under the name Nancy Shaw], as well as posters, a large pamphlet file, and other ephemera. The bulk of the collection focuses on Stoller's AIDS research for the book, Lessons from the Damned: Queers, Whores and Junkies Respond to AIDS. There is also material connected to, Women Resisting AIDS: Feminist Strategies of Empowerment, the book she co-edited with Beth E. Schneider. There are also some examples of her work on healthcare for prisoners and Latinas and breast cancer.
General
Finding Aid Written By:
Julia Bazar and Josue Hurtado
Date Completed:
June 2007
Access
Collection is open for research.
Alternate Forms Available
There are no alternate forms of this collection.
Acquisition Information
The collection was given to the Library in two parts - The bulk of the material in October 1999, and the rest given in July of 2002. Carton 9 and the oversize box were received in 2013. They are unprocessed.
System of Arrangement
Arranged to the folder level. Carton 9 and the oversize box were received as an addition in 2013 and are unprocessed and not included in the finding aid.
Biographical Information
Nancy Elaine Stoller was born in 1942 in Newport News, Virginia. In 1960 she left Virginia to attend Wellesley College in Wellesley, Massachusetts, where she earned an A.B. in Philosophy in 1963. She went on to earn her M.A. (1965) and Ph.D. (1972) in Sociology from Brandeis University in Waltham, Massachusetts. From 1978-1980 she was a Post-doctoral fellow at Yale University. Stoller started her job at University of California (UC) Santa Cruz in 1973 and received tenure in 1987 after having filed a gender discrimination suit against the University. Stoller worked and published under her married name, Nancy Shaw, for many years before reclaiming Stoller in the 1990s. Along with her work on AIDS, Stoller's research has focused on women, prisoners, and health care. Stoller became involved with the civil rights movement during her first year of college. She was involved in local actions in Wellesley and Boston during the school year and worked with the Washington D.CIRCA area Non-violent Action Group (DC-NAG) during the summer. Later she became involved with the Student Nonviolent Coordinating Committee (SNCC) and did organizing work in Maryland and Arkansas. Her activism continued throughout her life. In a recent, short, online biography she states:
I have been involved in various social change movements: anti-racism, feminism, anti-apartheid work, queer organizing, women's health activism, working on changing prison conditions, prison abolition, and so on.
After a brief marriage to Kevin (Kwame) Shaw (1966-1972) and the birth of her daughter, Gwendolyn, in 1968, Stoller came out as a lesbian. She was one of the first openly lesbian professors at UC Santa Cruz (UCSC) and was outed internationally during her tenure fight. Between her dismissal from UC Santa Cruz in 1984 and her reinstatement in 1987, Stoller worked as the Women's Program Development Director within the Education Department of the San Francisco AIDS Foundation (SFAF) from 1984 to 1987. While there she was involved with a number of projects including heterosexual focus groups, the drafting of a number of pamphlets, and the organization of women's support groups. This work led to further interactions with a variety of community based AIDS organizations. She did a formal participant/observer study of the New York City ACT-UP chapter in the fall/winter of 1989. She went to meetings and demonstrations, including the St. Patrick's Cathedral demonstration held in the December of that year. Stoller also spent significant time working with Cal-PEP, the California Prostitutes Education Project, an AIDS prevention and education organization founded and run by prostitutes and former prostitutes to prevent the spread of AIDS within that community. Stoller served as an advisor to the Executive Director of the organization, as well as doing a stint on the Board of Directors. Other groups that she had contact with during this period include: Prevention Point, a Needle Exchange program working with Intravenous (IV) Drug Users; the Women's AIDS Network (WAN), and Women's AIDS Risk Network (WARN). Stoller translated her experience working for SFAF and her interest in other AIDS related community organizations into two books on AIDS -Lessons from the Damned: Queers, Whores and Junkies Respond to AIDS published in 1998 and Women Resisting AIDS: Feminist Strategies of Empowerment (1995) co-edited by Stoller with Beth E. Schneider of UC Santa Barbara. Stoller wrote the chapter on "Lesbian Involvement in the AIDS Epidemic: Changing Roles and Generational Differences" in Women Resisting AIDS After returning to the UCSC campus she has taught classes in Transgressive Sexualities and Genders, Health and Human Rights in Prison, and Theory and Practice of Sexual Politics. The majority of Stoller's ongoing research has been into the treatment of women prisoners, especially in relation to medical care. She was also involved in an outreach study on breast cancer in the Latina community. As of 2005 Stoller is still teaching at UCSC and living in San Francisco.
Scope and Content of Collection
This collection consists predominantly of the research files used by Nancy Stoller in the writing of two books and a number of academic papers, and in teaching at the University of California Santa Cruz (UCSC). A high percentage of the collection is secondary source material including: newspaper and magazine articles, scholarly papers, documents (primarily minutes, publications, and other administrative or publicity materials) from a variety of community based, AIDS related organizations; a few posters; and a very extensive pamphlet collection. Primary documents include: drafts and published versions of papers written or co-written by Stoller, drafts of chapters and correspondence from Lessons from the Damned: Queers, Whores and Junkies Respond to AIDS, correspondence connected to Women Resisting AIDS: Feminist Strategies of Empowerment (1995), various handwritten notes, and two participant-observer notebooks from her time with ACT-UP New York. The collection also includes a small sampling of condoms and stickers, including some from Amsterdam, as well as dental dams and a leather harness for the dams. A small amount of material documenting some of her other research topics, as well as her later career at UCSC, can be found near the end of the collection. For material relating to Nancy Elaine Stoller (Nancy Stoller Shaw's) tenure battle with UCSC see the Nancy Shaw collection at the Gay Lesbian Bisexual Transgender Historical Society.
Stoller's interest in AIDS, as shown by her subject files, ranged widely beyond the gay white male model of the early epidemicirca Stoller collected popular and academic articles, pamphlets, clippings, organizational files, and other materials on Asian Americans, Latinos, Native Americans, African Americans, multicultural, and international issues. South Africa is represented by a series of posters and some other ephemera. Australia is represented by a number of research articles from Macquarie University, and the Netherlands (Holland) is represented by stickers and condoms as well as conference materials. A significant portion of the subject files concern women's issues including children and AIDS, education, heterosexual transmission, lesbians, perinatal transmission and pregnancy, prostitution, and women and AIDS. Ethics, demographics and the religious response are also covered.
The collection contains significant amounts of material on a number of agencies and organizations. The big three are the San Francisco AIDS Foundation (SFAF); the California Prostitute Education Project (Cal-PEP); and ACT-UP New York. Other organizations represented by multiple folders-worth of materials include: ACHA (American College Health Association - Task Force on the Acquired Immunodeficiency Syndrome (AIDS); APHA (American Public Health Association); City of New York and City of San Francisco Commissions on Human Rights; NSBC (National Skills Building Conference); WARN (Women and AIDS Risk Network); and University AIDS Events (and papers) from UCSF, UCB, UCSC, SFSU, and Macquarie University in Australia.
Other agencies and organizations documented to a greater or lesser extent include: AAPCHO (Association of Asian/Pacific Community Health Organization); AIDS Action Pledge, San Francisco; AIDS Health Project, San Francisco; California AIDS Project; SAMHA (Substance Abuse and Mental Health in AIDS); Santa Cruz AIDS Project; the Stop AIDS Project, San Francisco; WORLD (Women Organized to Respond to Life-threatening Diseases); AIDS Action Council; CARE AIDS (Prevention for Substance Abuse Treatment Programs, New York); Gay Men's Health Crisis [New York]; the National Gay Task Force (NGTF); and the New York City Task Force on Women & AIDS.
The collection is divided into 5 Series, based primarily on Stoller's own division of materials, and most of Stoller's folder headings and order have been retained, with occasional renaming of folders or subseries for clarity, and order imposed within or between topics/series/subseries when the original order was absent or unclear.
The series are: Series I: AIDS Subject Files; Series II: Organizations; Series III: Writings; Series IV: Administrative, Prison and Non-AIDS Files; Series V: Ephemera. Some of these series include subseries.
AIDS (Disease)--Political aspects--United States; AIDS (Disease)--Social Aspects--United States; AIDS (Disease)--Psychological aspects; AIDS (Disease) in women; AIDS (Disease)--Prevention; Intravenous drug abuse--Prevention; ACT UP New York (Organization); San Francisco AIDS Foundation; Cal-Pep (Organization); Stoller, Nancy E
- AIDS Subject Files, 1981-1995; Series 1; 144 Folders: Carton 1 Folders 1/1-1/71, Carton 2 Folders 2/1-2/73
  Scope and Contents
  This series consists of a variety of materials, from handwritten notes to newspaper clippings, arranged alphabetically by subject. Almost all of the material directly addresses AIDS or HIV infection; those that don't were clearly collected as background information on the subject. Other types of documents include photocopies of newspaper and magazine articles, whole magazines, scholarly papers, working documents or reports, statistical reports, some pamphlets or pamphlet drafts [see pamphlet subseries in the Ephemera Series for more pamphlets], etcetera Some individual items appear in more than one folder, because Stoller classified them that way. Information on similar topics can be found under different subject headings (i.e. even though there is a separate subject heading on "Prostitutes," a folder on "Women in the Sex Industry" can be found under "Women & AIDS.") Besides the Media subject file, which consists primarily of newspaper Clippings, several of the other subject files also contain "Media" folders and/or clippings mixed in with other documents. There are some drafts of articles in this series; see also Series III: Writings, for more materials written by Stoller.
  The subjects are arranged alphabetically and include: Asian-Americans and AIDS, Children and AIDS, Education, Epidemiology and Demographics, Ethics, Funding for AIDS Organizations, Heterosexuals and AIDS, International AIDS Conferences, International Concerns / AIDS and other Countries, Latino Issues, Lesbians, Media, Multicultural Concerns, Perinatal AIDS and Pregnancy, Prisoners and AIDS, Prostitution, PWA (People with AIDS), Religion, Research Articles, Resources, Risk, Safe(r) Sex, Treatment Issues, Women & AIDS, Workplace Issues, and AIDS Miscellaneous.
  Of special note are: 2 interviews in "Asian-Americans & AIDS - General Articles" folder; A draft of The Mental Health Impact of AIDS on Campus: A Handbook for College and University Counselors submitted to NIH in October 1987 by Johnson, Bassin & Shaw, Inc; and a photocopy of a photograph in the "Multicultural Concerns - Photocopy of Group Photo" folder, that appears to be of the Outreach Committee, mentioned in the previous folder.
  Wherever possible, original folder titles have been preserved.
  - Asian-Americans & AIDS (Carton 1, Folder 1-10)
    - "Asian Americans Responding to the AIDS Epidemic" by Christine Wong, 1993 (Carton 1, Folder 1)
    - Asian and Pacific Islander Statistics, 1992-1993 (Carton 1, Folder 2)
    - Chinese-Americans and AIDS, 1990 (Carton 1, Folder 3)
    - Filipinos and AIDS, 1990-1993 (Carton 1, Folder 4)
    - Japanese-Americans and AIDS, 1988; 1990-1993 (Carton 1, Folder 5)
    - Vietnamese-Americans and AIDS, 1988; undated (Carton 1, Folder 6)
    - Asian I.V. Drug Use and AIDS, circa 1987 (Carton 1, Folder 7)
    - Asian American Mental Health, 1986 (Carton 1, Folder 8)
    - Psychological Issues, 1986; undated (Carton 1, Folder 9)
    - General Articles, 1988-1993 (Carton 1, Folder 10)
  - Children & AIDS (Carton 1, Folder 11-17)
    - "AIDS and Your Child", circa 1985 (Carton 1, Folder 11)
    - Children with AIDS, circa 1987 (Carton 1, Folder 12)
    - Education of Infected Children, 1986 (Carton 1, Folder 13)
    - Care of Infants, Mothers & Preschoolers, 1986; undated (Carton 1, Folder 14)
    - Media Clips, 1985 (Carton 1, Folder 15)
    - Information AIDS/Kids, 1985 (Carton 1, Folder 16)
    - Teenagers and AIDS, 1985-1992 (Carton 1, Folder 17)
  - Education (Carton 1, Folder 18-21)
    - Catalogs, 1988 (Carton 1, Folder 18)
    - Videotapes/Audio-visuals, 1988 (Carton 1, Folder 19)
    - AIDS in the University, 1987-1990; undated (Carton 1, Folder 20)
    - Prevention of Transmission in School, 1985 (Carton 1, Folder 21)
  - Epidemiology and Demographics (Carton 1, Folder 22-29)
    - Epidemiological and Demographics Surveillance Reports of California, 1985-1988 (Carton 1, Folder 22)
    - CDC Surveillance Forms [blank], undated (Carton 1, Folder 23)
    - MMWR Reports on AIDS, 1985-1986 (Carton 1, Folder 24)
    - California AIDS Update, Office of AIDS, 1988 (Carton 1, Folder 25)
    - San Francisco Epidemiological Bulletin, 1987-1989 (Carton 1, Folder 26)
    - AIDS Reported Cases, etcetera, 1987-1989 (Carton 1, Folder 27)
    - Focus: A Guide to AIDS Research and Counseling, 1989-1990 (Carton 1, Folder 28)
    - An Updated Quantitative Analysis of AIDS in California, 1987 (Carton 1, Folder 29)
  - Ethics: Newsletter and Conference, 1987; 1990 (Carton 1, Folder 30)
  - Funding for AIDS Organizations, 1992 (Carton 1, Folder 31)
  - Heterosexuals and AIDS (Carton 1, Folder 32-36)
    - Media Articles, 1985-1987 (Carton 1, Folder 32)
    - Baseline Survey of Heterosexuals, 1988 (Carton 1, Folder 33)
    - Sexual Transmission of HIV, 1986 (Carton 1, Folder 34)
    - Results of Qualitative Study on Heterosexuals, 1986 (Carton 1, Folder 35)
    - AIDS and the Sex Therapist, 1985 (Carton 1, Folder 36)
  - International AIDS Conferences (Carton 1, Folder 37-41)
    - 4th International Conference on AIDS - Stockholm, 1988 (Carton 1, Folder 37)
    - 6th & 7th International Conferences on AIDS (SF & Florence), 1988-1995 (Carton 1, Folder 38)
    - 8th International Conference on AIDS - Amsterdam (Carton 1, Folder 39-40)
      - Transcripts, 1992 (Carton 1, Folder 39)
      - Program/Notes, 1992 (Carton 1, Folder 40)
    - International AIDS Women's Caucus (D.C) & 7th International Conference of People with AIDS (Cape Town), 1995 (Carton 1, Folder 41)
  - International Concerns / AIDS and other Countries (Carton 1, Folder 42-46)
    - Africa, 1990-1995; undated (Carton 1, Folder 42)
    - Asia, 1992-1993 (Carton 1, Folder 43)
    - Australia, 1989-1992 (Carton 1, Folder 44)
    - Latin America, 1991-1993; undated (Carton 1, Folder 45)
    - South East Asia, 1991-1992 (Carton 1, Folder 46)
  - Latino Issues - Health Policy and AIDS, 1992-1994 (Carton 1, Folder 47)
  - Lesbians (Carton 1, Folder 48-63)
    - Safe Sex, 1991-1992 (Carton 1, Folder 48)
    - Safe Sex/Final Group Project Report [Student Paper], circa 1992 (Carton 1, Folder 49)
    - AIDS Education, 1990 (Carton 1, Folder 50)
    - SCWU (Southern California Women for Understanding) Pamphlet on Lesbians & draft SFAF (San Francisco AIDS Foundation) Lesbian Brochure, 1986 (Carton 1, Folder 51)
    - Health Issues, 1986-1987 (Carton 1, Folder 52)
    - "Lesbians AIDS" by Nisa Donnelly, 1986 (Carton 1, Folder 53)
    - "Lesbians and AIDS" Brochure [draft], undated (Carton 1, Folder 54)
    - "The Impact of AIDS on the Lesbian Community" [draft] by Beth Schneider, 1986 (Carton 1, Folder 55)
    - "Lesbians Working in AIDS" by Judy Macks, undated (Carton 1, Folder 56)
    - Lesbian Insemination Project, 1984-1987 (Carton 1, Folder 57)
    - Lesbian IVDU (Intravenous Drug Users) Project, 1987 (Carton 1, Folder 58)
    - NLGHF (National Lesbian Gay Health Foundation) Lesbian Health Care Survey Reports, 1986-1987 (Carton 1, Folder 59)
    - Research, 1987-1988 (Carton 1, Folder 60)
    - Notes, 1986-1987; undated (Carton 1, Folder 61)
    - SOL Presentation, undated (Carton 1, Folder 62)
    - UCLA, February 21, 1987 (Carton 1, Folder 63)
  - Media, Carton 1 Folder 64-Carton 2 Folder 7
    - Media Contacts, undated (Carton 1, Folder 64)
    - Miscellaneous notes, correspondence & articles, 1985; undated (Carton 1, Folder 65)
    - KRON-Life and Death at the Ambassador Hotel, 1994 (Carton 1, Folder 66)
    - City on a Hill [UCSC student newspaper], 1987 (Carton 1, Folder 67)
    - On Our Backs, 1984-1985 (Carton 1, Folder 68)
    - People Magazine, 1988 (Carton 1, Folder 69)
    - Plexus, 1984; 1987 (Carton 1, Folder 70)
    - Published Articles, 1985-1989 (Carton 1, Folder 71)
    - AIDS and Prisoners - Newspaper Clippings, 1985 (Carton 2, Folder 1)
    - Newspaper Clippings (Carton 2, Folder 2-6)
      - 1984-1985 (Carton 2, Folder 2)
      - 1985-1987 (Carton 2, Folder 3)
      - 1987-1991 (Carton 2, Folder 4)
      - 1991-1994 (Carton 2, Folder 5)
      - 1995 (Carton 2, Folder 6)
    - Non-AIDS Newspaper Clippings, 1987-1991 (Carton 2, Folder 7)
  - Multicultural Concerns (Carton 2, Folder 8-23)
    - SFAF Ethnic Outreach Committee, 1986-1989 (Carton 2, Folder 8)
    - Ethnic Outreach Research, 1986 (Carton 2, Folder 9)
    - Minority Group Report, 1986 (Carton 2, Folder 10)
    - Photocopy of Group, undated (Carton 2, Folder 11)
    - Minority/Women owned Businesses, 1986 (Carton 2, Folder 12)
    - Community Meetings, 1986 (Carton 2, Folder 13)
    - Ethnic Minority Focus Group [Overhead transparencies], undated (Carton 2, Folder 14)
    - General Articles and Notes, 1984-1987 (Carton 2, Folder 15)
    - MIRA(Multicultural Inquiry & Research on AIDS) Newsletter, 1987-1988 (Carton 2, Folder 16)
    - Health Care and Minorities, 1976-1990 (Carton 2, Folder 17)
    - American Blacks, 1987-1991 (Carton 2, Folder 18)
    - Black Community - KWIC FAN (Kapuna West Inner-City Child/Family Network [AIDS Trainings], 1986-1987 (Carton 2, Folder 19)
    - American Indians, 1986; undated (Carton 2, Folder 20)
    - AIDS Education and Support Services to Minorities: A Survey of Community Based AIDS Service Providers, National AIDS Network (DC), April 1987 (Carton 2, Folder 21)
    - Pacific Center AIDS Project, circa 1985 (Carton 2, Folder 22)
    - Media Clippings, 1987; undated (Carton 2, Folder 23)
  - Perinatal and Pregnancy (Carton 2, Folder 24-28)
    - SFDPH (San Francisco Department of Public Health) Guidelines, 1986 (Carton 2, Folder 24)
    - "Guidelines for the Control of Perinatally Transmitted Human Immunodeficiency Virus Infection and Care of Infected Mothers, Infants and Children" Published in the Western Journal of Medicine; (N. Shaw is listed as one of the authors), 1987 (Carton 2, Folder 25)
    - Workplace Issues, 1985 (Carton 2, Folder 26)
    - Drugs/Pregnancy, 1981; 1987 (Carton 2, Folder 27)
    - Pregnancy Pamphlets, undated (Carton 2, Folder 28)
  - Prostitution (Carton 2, Folder 29-32)
    - Prostitution and Feminism, circa 1991 (Carton 2, Folder 29)
    - Association Aspasie (Swiss Prostitute's Organization and changing the UN Charter), 1991 (Carton 2, Folder 30)
    - The Oldest Profession Times, 1985; 1986 (Carton 2, Folder 31)
    - Media Clippings, 1985; undated (Carton 2, Folder 32)
  - PWA (People with AIDS) (Carton 2, Folder 33-35)
    - PWA Coalition and ACT NOW Chapter, 1989; undated (Carton 2, Folder 33)
    - The Body Positive: A Magazine about HIV, June 1990 (Carton 2, Folder 34)
    - Adair & Armstrong Film - "Absolutely Positive: A Film about Living with AIDS, 1989 (Carton 2, Folder 35)
  - Religion - AIDS and the Catholic Church, 1988 (Carton 2, Folder 36)
  - Research Articles (Carton 2, Folder 37-39)
    - Prevention Research, 1986-1991 (Carton 2, Folder 37)
    - Relman, Arnold - Ethical Issues, 1985 (Carton 2, Folder 38)
    - Research Articles - Various, 1985-1987; 1993 (Carton 2, Folder 39)
  - Resources (Carton 2, Folder 40-41)
    - AIDS Resource Lists and Bibliography, circa 1987; 1988 (Carton 2, Folder 40)
    - Resources/Referrals, 1985; undated (Carton 2, Folder 41)
  - Risk (Carton 2, Folder 42-44)
    - Albert Bandura - "Perceived Self-Efficacy in Exercise of Control Over AIDS Infection", 1987 (Carton 2, Folder 42)
    - Nancy Adler - "Changing Risk Behaviors: Fear, Rationality and Decision-making", circa 1984 (Carton 2, Folder 43)
    - Risk Evaluation Notes, undated (Carton 2, Folder 44)
  - Safe(r) Sex (Carton 2, Folder 45-48)
    - Safer Sex - UCSC Workshop, written and compiled by Richard D. Lightfoot, circa 1989 (Carton 2, Folder 45)
    - Davira Shin - Sexology Instructor, circa 1989 (Carton 2, Folder 46)
    - Guidelines for Women, 1985; 1988,; undated (Carton 2, Folder 47)
    - Promoting Safer Sex: International Workshop, 1989 (Carton 2, Folder 48)
  - Treatment Issues (Carton 2, Folder 49-54)
    - Alternative Treatments for AIDS/Alta Wellness, 1990 (Carton 2, Folder 49)
    - AZT Update, 1987-1992; undated (Carton 2, Folder 50)
    - SF General Hospital Ribaviran, 1985 (Carton 2, Folder 51)
    - HPA-23, 1985 (Carton 2, Folder 52)
    - Anti-AIDS Drugs, 1985 (Carton 2, Folder 53)
    - Therapies, undated (Carton 2, Folder 54)
  - Women & AIDS (Carton 2, Folder 55-70)
    - Bibliography, 1991 (Carton 2, Folder 55)
    - NIMH/NIDA Women and AIDS Research Conference, 1987 (Carton 2, Folder 56)
    - Media Clippings, 1985-1988 (Carton 2, Folder 57)
    - Politics of Survival [excerpts], undated (Carton 2, Folder 58)
    - SFAF's Women and AIDS Clinical Resource Guide, 1987; undated (Carton 2, Folder 59)
    - Correspondence RE: Clinical Resource Guide, 1987 (Carton 2, Folder 60)
    - Women & AIDS - Clinical Resource Packet, 1985-1986 (Carton 2, Folder 61)
    - Women at Risk [Conference] and background articles, 1982-1984; 1987 (Carton 2, Folder 62)
    - Transmission, 1986-1987 (Carton 2, Folder 63)
    - Women in the Sex Industry, 1985 (Carton 2, Folder 64)
    - Alcoholism Center, undated (Carton 2, Folder 65)
    - SFAF in Feminine Connection, 1985 (Carton 2, Folder 66)
    - Interview with Constance Wofsy in BETA (Bulletin of Experimental Treatments for AIDS), 1991 (Carton 2, Folder 67)
    - Research Papers, 1987; 1991 (Carton 2, Folder 68)
    - Women's Health Concerns, 1987; 1989 (Carton 2, Folder 69)
    - Miscellaneous, 1987-1995 (Carton 2, Folder 70)
  - Work Place Issues - AIDS in the Workplace, circa 1990s (Carton 2, Folder 71)
  - Miscellaneous AIDS (Carton 2, Folder 72-73)